http://aztectent.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
A-Aztec Rents & Sells Inc, DBA Aztec Tents Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.aztectent.com (the “Site”).
PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
- “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.
HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:
Communicate with you;
Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).
SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store-- you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:
https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.
You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by visiting:
FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
GOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
BING - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.
DO NOT TRACK
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
YOUR RIGHTS
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.
DATA RETENTION
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
MINORS
The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 18.
CHANGES
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
CONTACT US
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at sales@aztectents.com or by mail using the details provided below:
2665 Columbia Street, Torrance, CA, 90503, United States
Frame Tents
Pole Tents
Clearspan Structures
Compatible Plus
Accessories
Specialty Tents
School Space­™ Solutions
Fabric Partition Systems
Frame Tents
Frame Tents feature a skeleton of aluminum framework and steel connectors to support the tent top. Although this style of tent is "free-standing" by design, it still must be anchored to resist wind forces. All styles of frame tents have no poles that come to the ground in the interior space of the tent.
Frame Tents
Pole Tents
Pole tents rely on tension in the membrane to hold the shape of the tent system. These tents are supported by single or multiple centerpoles in the middle of the tent area and a series of sidepoles around the perimeter of the tent area. The tent is tensioned toward the anchoring locations commonly with a rope or ratchet strap.
Pole Tents
Clearspan Structures
Similar to Frame Tents, these types of frame supported structures have no interior posts or columns. The unique attribute that Clearspan Structures hold is their ability to span quite large distances without interior posts and also without external guying. Generally, these structures are built for higher loading applications and larger span sizes.
Clearspan Structures
Compatible Plus
'Compatible-Plus®' products are aesthetically and structurally indistinguishable from their competitive counterparts. However, the new series have been re-engineered, incorporating proprietary improvements to their structural quality and integrity. These options allow the tent industry customers to purchase from the vendor they deem best.
Compatible Plus
Accessories
Accessories include liners, legs skirts, doors, raingutters, and materials for repair & replacement parts
Accessories
Specialty Tents
These products are geared for specific applications and are often seen as non-mainstream products. Generally these products are built on an as needed basis and are generally not "on the shelf".
Specialty Tents
School Space­™ Solutions
These sturdy frame tents have been designed for their adaptability in size and layout configurations. Perfect for expanding outdoor educational facilities or offering new and innovative ways to socially distance.
School Space­™ Solutions
Fabric Partition Systems
We offer a wide selection of fabric panel systems designed for various indoor partition applications. These solutions have applications in medical facilities, offices, retail establishments, restaurants, and manufacturing plants.
Fabric Partition Systems
Mobile Menu
Products
About
Videos
News
Inquiries
Client Resources
This site uses cookies to provide you with a great user experience. By using , you accept our use of cookies. Continue
